No living creature was hurt during
the production of this show.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
Murderer!
Goktug!
Boran.
Many valiant alps of ours...
our Beys...
were murdered...
stabbing them in the back...
How to charge them?
The bloody-handed murderers
tried to kill our traditions...
They tried to end us...
What does our religion say,
Sheik Edebalı?
As it is written in Bakarah surah,
Osman Bey...
Retalition is good for us.
Now...
Before dying...
What are your final words?
I've come this land to finish...
what my father Noyan...
left unfinished.
I came to...
end...
your generation.
Now I am kneeling in front of Gokboru...
who is from Khan Tengri.
Do I kneel because I seek forgiveness?
Never.
I kneel because I respect Gokboru
who managed to...
defeat many Noyans
supported by dark souls...
and Genghis Khan's valiant wolves.
When I first saw you...
You told me that you were going to...
rip me apart under the blue sky.
Keep your promise, Gokboru.
Geyhatu's Hunter Dog...
Black Shaman Togay...
You defeated him.
You defeated me with your commitment...
to your herd.
Perform the justice of your generation,
the justice of...
Khan Tengri...
Osman Bey.
Osman Bey!
Victory goes to the ones whose swords are
sharpened with faith.
Victory goes to the ones who fight
shoulder to shoulder...
and move together.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
(In the name of Allah, the compassionate, the merciful)
My Bey!
The double swords my Bamsı Bey...
gave to me.
They have been waiting for this moment.
I can't relieve no matter...
what we do to them.
My Osman, you shall live long.
You shall live long.
Dears!
Today, we refresh ourselves.
Those snakes thought that...
we forget our pain and not chase
them.
Those snakes thought that...
we wouldn't take revenge...
but...
Dark Osman Bey...
brought them to me with the
help of his paw like an eagle.
Allah-u Akbar.
(Allah is the greatest.)
Ertugrul Ghazi's son Osman Bey...
gave everyone what they deserved...
no matter what their religion is...
what nationality they are.
Our enemies can gather up and push us!
They can push us with slyness,
with cruelty...
They can try to stab us in the back.
As long as our brotherhood remains...
As long as my generation is there...
Justice will always be performed
in this land.
Neither Mongols nor Byzantine has
power to...
undo what I say!
May your justice be everlasting, Osman Bey
Long live Osman Bey.
Allah-u Akbar.
(Allah is the greatest.)
Osman took Togay away from my hands!
Togay is a rebel who disobeyed.
Look at the bright side.
Osman Bey saved you from a trouble.
I should have made Togay pay.
Not a Turk!
Your soldiers dropped the ball...
Osman Bey caught it.
That he killed Togay saved both you and
me from a huge trouble. Accept it.
Also, we have issues to take care of
before talking about Osman and Togay.
Your taxes create uneasiness everywhere.
The cruelty of your soldiers increase
the number of rebels.
I won't let Osman go before
I punish him, Sultan Mesut.
Does Osman Bey pay his taxes?
He does.
Is he loyal to our agreement?
He is.
If you chase vengeance...
Taxes won't be the only thing you lose...
You also draw Geyhatu's anger on you.
It'll be my problem too.
I don't want to draw Geyhatu's
anger on me.
Osman will pay a price...
But not with blood, with gold instead.
What do you think?
The price for taking Togay away from me...
costs him a tax of three years.
Isn't this too much?
Disorder will take place in Bıtinya...
if you try to ruin them.
Also, are you sure that Osman
was the one...
who took Togay?
Are you kidding me, Sultan Mesut?
I am not stupid enough to believe that
Osman didn't do this.
You don't have a proof.
I don't think Osman Bey and the other Beys
deserve this tax.
I don't care about what you think.
I'll have a stableman to tame a horse
like Osman.
What does this mean?
Nicola agaisnt Osman.
I'll have Nicola as my man.
Only Nicola can handle that
brutal stallion.
Nicola is handy, we know that.
If you send soldiers to Nicola to
support him...
that will mess the whole Bithynia.
You have to calculate the end.
I won't send soldier to Nicola.
I will send gold to Nicola
to take care of him.
Thank my holy Lord that we
destroyed our enemies one by one.
- Thanks to him.
Now, there's only Nicola left.
Sooner or later, we'll take
care of him too.
- Inshallah (If Allah permits.)
- Inshallah.
Osman Bey...
Yes, Umur Bey.
Before I go back to my tent,
I have something to tell you.
Time has proved you right, Osman Bey.
While we remained
in the darkness of excuses...
The light of the tradition shined on you.
While we acted selfish,
arguing for nothing...
You only cared our unitiy.
We came and saw that you are the one.
And you are the one to judge.
Estagfurullah (not at all).
Estagfurullah Umur Bey.
The one who judges is...
Allah.
What we need to do is to work.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
We united the tribes.
My Bey father and my Bey goes shoulder
to shoulder. No one can stop us.
Our struggle has just getting started,
Malhun Hatun.
Togay dies, another one comes.
However, we won't stop!
We will be riding high in the saddle
to the horizon we believe in.
Togay messed up with the wrong people.
He paid for it with his life.
Osman killed Togay but...
you send him to the death's door.
Who do you think is the winner now?
Is it Osman or you?
Osman benefited as much as you did.
Moreover, he gained dignity in front of
Turk Beys as he killed that barbar in Sogut.
This Osman will blow up in
our hands, Nicola.
Or he will bring us new opportunuties,
Yason.
- Mikis.
- Sir.
Mongol messenger came from
Konya to see you.
Let our precious guest in.
We are honoured, my messenger.
Welcome.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
(In the name of Allah, the merciful, the compassionate.)
The warrior of Ghazis Bamsı Bey.
The fellow of Ertugrul Bey.
The head of Kayı Alps.
You ended the enemy of our tribe.
You did never let Kayıs down.
Now...
your sons...
took revenge for you.
We didn't let you down.
You used to run to a war to another
without sleep.
Now sleep well.
Sleep well.
Don't worry about us.
Cerkutay, come.
Come.
You have just met Bamsı Bey.
Yet you still cry.
Think about what our feelings are.
Okay.
Don't be shy.
Pour out your heart.
Don't worry about us.
Father.
I have your swords.
I am trying to use them both.
I clean your tent everyday.
I wake up in the night and pray for you.
If I have a son, I'll name him Bamsı.
I'll tell him about you.
You will.
You'll get married.
You'll have children.
Alps!
We will be ready everytime.
We shall not stop from now on!
We shall not!
We will continue until our swords break,
until the last drop of our blood.
For Bamsı Bey!
Allah-u Akbar!
(Allah is the greatest!)
To be honest, messenger.
I am shocked.
How can such a loyal commander...
rebel to Geyhatu?
Ah Osman.
Togay called him Gokboru.
It is a wolf that comes only in one
thousand years, something like that.
I can now see what he meant.
Gokboru hah?
While Osman curshed Togay like a mouse
that raided his barn...
He talked like a rebel, like a
threat to Geyhatu...
not like a Bey who only pays
his taxes.
So, he challanged Yargucu.
Osman Bey will be trouble to you,
not to us.
Governor Nicola.
Sooner or later.
He'll conquer your castle first.
Like how his father conquered Karacahisar,
and like how he conquered Kulucahisar.
The time passed.
The tribes who rebels to Sultan and
Geyhatu...
will come this land, won't they?
Yes they will!
Will Osman chase them?
He will.
Will he pay tax to Geyhatu?
He won't!
If my castle falls...
Yargucu will be dead.
Yes he will be.
We can beat Osman with our
one finger.
Oh, be careful there.
Be careful, he may break that finger.
We both want to stop Osman.
It'll be good for both of us.
A strong army will solve the problem.
As you know, the best Turk...
is the dead Turk.
You know we don't want a war.
Governor Nicola.
What is your proposal...
dear messenger?
Governor Yargucu will support you...
on the struggle between you and Osman.
We have a saying.
- talks in Greek -
Do not be anyone's toy.
If you will, there must be a price.
A carriage full of gold is on its way to
here from Konya.
It will arrive in Inegol if I don't...
stop it.
Do you like it?
Do you have a saying for this?
Some lives must be lifeless.
If glorious Yargucu is going to help me...
to destroy Osman, I cannot refuse...
dear messenger.
Your loyalty will make Governor
Yargucu happy.
Do not be anyone's toy.
Welcome Osman Bey.
Welcome my Bey.
Welcome my Osman Bey.
Brother, I want to talk to my Beys.
Eyvallah (okay) Osman Bey.
Baysungur.
Turanalp!
My Bey.
You honored your name.
We punished Togay,
we secured the justice.
Eyvallah (thanks) my Bey.
My only aim is to be a martyr in
the direction of your sword.
Eyvallah. (thanks).
Eyvallah.
You said he couldn't manage but, he
brought us Togay. Mashallah (praise be).
And Osman Bey sees it.
Now, As Osman Bey's Alp...
You need to do what you have to do.
Eyvallah brother.
You are right.
Oh my brother.
This is how Osman Bey's alp acts.
Put the rugs in a different chest, Alaca.
- What are these for?
- Keep up.
These are all my mother's handcraft.
As we told her to stop, she
would stare at us...
and say "These will decorate a
bride's dowery."
Being Umur Bey's Hatun requires diligince.
She used to control the whole tribe.
She used to overcome.
She used to stitch these if she has any
time left.
You passed away early, my valiant mother.
Store the ornamental rugs in a differnet
chest, Alaca.
Why are we doing this, Malhun Hatun?
I really wonder.
They have been in the chest since we
came here. I want to please my mother.
They shall decorate Osman Bey's tent.
May my mother rest in peace.
Does Bala Hatun know about this?
She doesn't need to know.
The tent is Osman Bey's.
I am a Hatun of this tent.
Did you settle down in there?
Of course I did.
Not only Osman, but also his whole
tribe is in my hands.
I'll cause Turks' extinction
sooner or later.
But first, I'll destroy Osman's hopes
to have a child.
With...
with your soft hands.
Malhun loves me like a sister.
She trusts me, she listens to me.
My soft eyes are enough to scratch their
eyes out.
Zoe, my little venomous snake.
Tell me.
Where should I begin?
Malhun Hatun, Alaca...
Umur Bey...
Goktug.
Silly lover.
Is this silly lover under your spell?
Spell? Let's call it witchery.
Zoe, I want you to enhance your contacts.
Be my shadow until I hit the
last time.
Not only what you hear and see...
I want to know what you smell, what you feel.
What I smell
is sheep.
What I feel is the taste of
the pain I'll give them.
Trust your loyal servant Zoe, sir.
I won't get out of there
without my prey.
Goktug must have missed you.
Go.
No, this silence is not good.
Governor Yargucu must have learned
we took Togay.
My Bey, are those cruels going to
attack us with an army?
Mongols have many troubles
to deal with.
Our Turkmen brothers support us.
In this mess, they can't
gather an army to attack us.
However, we are going to take
precautions.
Can I come in my Bey?
Come!
My Bey, Mongols sent a messenger.
Speak of the devil, and he appears.
Let him come.
I came here under the order of glorious
Ilhanlı State's holy heir Yargucu.
Speak.
You know why I am here.
You executed Togay, Osman Bey.
That's fine.
What else does your governor want?
The price.
The price, huh?
What is the price? Tell me.
You'll pay your three-year tax
in three days.
This is the punihment you are given.
Three days huh?
Three days.
If you don't deliver the gold in time...
It'll mean you violated the
agreement with Yargucu.
Ilhanlı State will not come to
take gold...
We'll come to kill.
Three days it is.
You shall leave.
We are going to prepare the gold.
So, my Beys.
Tell me.
You all heard.
What do you think?
Let's say we paid them...
What are we going to do?
We can't afford any of the needs.
We'll have to stop the charities
in Sogut.
We can't even afford Alps.
And they won't stop, they'll
want more.
Our only choice is war.
They are cornering us.
This is why they want too much.
They want us to fail to pay.
They are trying hold us responsible
for the war.
I have an agreement with Sultan.
It is not appropriate for me to do
something without his information.
After all...
After all, he risked his throne to
support us.
I'll think it through.
Then I'll decide.
Governer Yargucu's gold
will arrive tomorrow.
Dimitri, you'll welcome the soldiers.
I can't rest until I see the gold
in my castle.
How can I do it?
I like to take precautions.
Take precautions so that
you can sleep well, Dimitri.
Yes, sir.
We'll create a new army with the gold, sir.
I'll create an army of randy fighters,
not an army of lazy peasants, Helen.
You'll go to the bazaar of fighters
with the gold.
We'll create an army of Maceds. Catalans,
the pirates, the barbarians who..
are ready to do anything for us.
Dimitri, take your soldiers and leave.
Bring me my gold safe and sound.
Yes sir.
In this land where the tables can turn
upside down anytime...
Togay's death brought us gold, Helen.
Now it's time to use that opportunity,
Nicola.
We don't have a second to lose.
Start working already.
Helena, we are stronger than before.
We have eyes in the tribe.
Zoe has sharp eyes.
But her teeth are sharper.
The immigrants will be fed in the cook
tent until they can earn their keep.
We have more expenses, my Osman.
As long as Sogut grows...
our expenses can be more, that's fine,
my Bala.
We'll take care of it,
Inshallah (if Allah permits).
We will.
My Bala...
I want Malhun Hatun to come to Sogut, too.
I want her to help on cook tent.
Gonca helps me, thank her.
- I don't need anyone else.
- Malhun Hatun can join you.
She can help you,
she'll be handy.
If you say so.
My Bala...
It's not easy.
She used to do the all work in
her tent.
She was to decide, she was to fight
without a Bey.
Now, she is just sitting in the tent.
She is not used to this.
We have to give her some
space to work.
This is true.
She is this tent's Hatun as well.
She has every right.
Can I come in my Bey?
Be patient my Bala.
Be patient.
Come Baysungur.
Be patient Bala.
Be patient.
A letter from our Sultan, my Bey.
Is everything ready, my Gonca?
Don't worry, my Bala.
Everything is ready.
Okay, the tribe is entrusted to you.
Malhun Hatun, I am going to the
cook tent. You shall come with me.
Of course, that'd be great.
I have other things to do, Bala Hatun.
I'll come when I am available.
We can solve if there's any problem.
Cook tent has no problem to solve.
If you want to help like everyone else do,
you are welcomed.
Right. People should compete
when it comes to charity.
Let's leave, Bala Hatun. Malhun Hatun will
join when she is ready.
See you.
Let's go.
We finished fast.
Mashallah (praise be).
I have never seen a bigger dowery
in my life.
Your turn is next.
So, Zoe, shall we have an Alp from Kayı
tribe for you and Alaca.
Alaca Hatun?
There are enough alps in
Umur Bey's tent, Malhun Hatun.
Calm down, Alaca. Okay.
There are chests to open.
We have to settle down.
Finish before it gets dark.
- Boran.
- My Bey.
Wait until Mongols move away.
Yes my Bey.
Cover the chests with these red cloths.
What are these?
What are you doing?
We are changing the rugs.
Did anyone let you do that?
We asked Malhun Hatun, Gonca Hatun.
Do you hear what you say, Hatun?
Don't you know who is the Hatun
of this tent?
Am I not this tent's Hatun?
Don't you know that?
You are.
Of course you are.
They are performing my order.
If you came to help, come help.
If you won't, leave.
Go on, Hatuns.
Do you want to say anything, Hatun?
Here is the door.
Get ready! Get in the position!
Get in the position!
Come here, Dimitri.
Kill me.
Nikola will take care of you.
Tell Nikola that...
even if he hides behind the Mongols...
I will be the one who kills him.
My Bey is coming.
We saved our golds from the heathens.
Now, it's time to use them for good.
Come on, Alps!
We're going back to the tent.
Thank you.
Bala.
My Gonca.
- Why are you in such a hurry?
- My Bala.
- You should come to the tent.
- What happened?
Malhun Hatun.
How did he know? How did Osman
know that the golds were there?
How? How did he learn?
How did he learn? How did he learn?
- How did he learn?
- Dimitri doesn't know that, sir.
Helen, shut up!
Shut up!
Sir, we have a letter from our Emperor.
Nikola.
The Emperor...
wants me to go to İznik to talk to my son.
Why?
Every human seals his
or her own fate, Helen.
I'm going to read my own fate.
We did good, Osman Bey.
Sultan Mesut wrote that the governor
will send Nikola the golds.
He wants to punish you.
What will we do, Osman Bey?
We will have the
golds that the governor sent.
Osman Bey...
won't it make the
Ilkhanate angry towards us?
We won't have the Mongols' golds, brother.
We will have Nikola's golds.
We killed two birds with one stone.
We prevented Nikola
from going stronger and...
we will pay our taxes to Mongols.
With their own golds.
Malhun Hatun.
How could you do that without telling me?
Keep calm, Bala Hatun.
You shouldn't be that angry.
I brought some stuff from my dowery.
Malhun Hatun.
It's a Bey tent.
Everything has a meaning here.
You can't bring everything you want.
As you said, Bala Hatun.
Everything is more meaningful now.
It's seen that Malhun Hatun is here.
Is that why you're here?
Are you here to spoil everything?
You have your own tent, Hatun.
You do whatever you wish there.
You shall not mess here.
Bala Hatun.
Beys are back.
Let's meet them.
Thank you!
- May your war be holy, my Bey.
- Thank you.
Mashallah!
May your war be holy, Osman Bey.
Thank you, Malhun Hatun.
We have got some news.
You hurt the heathens again.
We'll shed more blood until we take...
Bamsı Bey's revenge.
- May Allah protect your sword.
- Amin. Inshallah.
I made food for you.
Come to my meal if you're hungry.
I should talk to my Beys.
Later, Inshallah.
- My Bey.
- My Bala.
May your war be holy.
Thank you.
- Salam Alaikum, Master Davut.
- Alaikum Salam.
- May it be easy.
- Do it if it is easy.
It's my father's job.
Hit then.
- Mashallah.
- Thank you.
- Tell me, what did happen?
- We got the golds for Nikola.
Good.
- Allah is right.
- Allah is eternal.
- Salam Alaikum, Master Davut.
- Alaikum Salam.
- Osman Bey is waiting for you.
- Why?
You did good, Turan Alp.
It's not a big deal.
Don't say that. You're
good for a new comer.
I am the soldier of Kayı Tent.
Kayı Tent's duties are hard.
The fate is the same.
We are martyrs if we die, we
are Ghazis if we stay.
- Allah is right.
- Allah is eternal.
Mongols wanted to...
empower Nikola.
He wanted to get soldiers with
these golds and attack us.
You spoiled their plans, my Bey.
They shouldn't be angrier.
We didn't get these golds from the
Mongols. Why do they be angry?
We got them from our enemies.
And...
the golds that Mongols want from us...
here are the golds.
They won't like it as they
will have their own golds.
They will see what happens if
they play trick to Kayıs.
Yes.
What you have done will be known
by everyone.
Our Ghazis will be proud of you.
More Ghazis will join us.
We will be ready.
We will have thousands of...
soldiers and Ghazis.
That's what my father wanted.
Inshallah.
We will be united.
Thank you, brother.
We will move step by step
and we will be careful.
If Nikola is that closer to Mongols...
it will continue.
However, we will be careful.
We will destroy Nikola...
without letting Mongols know.
May Allah make you powerful, Osman Bey.
If you'll excuse me.
I do.
Send these golds to our Sultan, to Konya.
Your command, my Bey.
We will go to Sheikh Edebalı's lodge
tonight...
together.
Your command, my Bey.
Akça Dervish.
We have talked about justice.
What is justice?
Something stays where it
belongs, that is justice.
What is injustice?
It's putting something
where it doesn't belong to.
Yes.
Now...
tell me, Kumral Abdal.
When will injustice be legitimate?
Never, my Sheikh.
What if it is for Allah's consent?
Injustice can't happen...
even if it's for Allah.
Yes.
You tell me, Osman Bey.
Can you do injustice for the state's good?
The state...
provides justice, my Sheikh.
Injustice can't be a thing
what state does.
Will an Alp do injustice...
for a Bey's good?
No, my Sheikh.
He shouldn't.
Even if it is towards a heathen?
He shouldn't, my Sheikh.
Mashallah.
My Sheikh...
We will come again
tomorrow with Boran Alp.
And we will establish
justice in front of the lodge.
Are you stealing food again, Cerkutay?
I always eat at this time
Bamsı Bey would eat at this time.
Isn't a plate enough for you?
Not for me.
For Bamsı Bey.
Bamsı Bey...
For Bamsı Bey?
I know, Aygül.
Bamsı Bey is martryed.
However, I can't accept it.
Cerkutay...
Some wounds...
never heal, I know.
In Bamsı Bey's tent...
it's hard to live without him, right?
I'm alone too.
In a tent, alone.
I think of so many things.
Do you think I don't know that, mad girl?
You're right.
I know what you do in the tent.
Don't think too much.
Eat your food.
Stop.
Isn't it for...
Bamsı Bey?
He won't be angry as I give it to you.
My Bala.
How are the things going in cook tent?
Is everything okay?
Everyone's needs are fulfilled.
Did Malhun Hatun help?
She couldn't come.
She had more important job in her tent.
What is that?
She wanted some of our stuff
in our tent to change.
She didn't like them, I guess.
Everyone has a different taste.
She wanted to make some changes.
She is the Hatun of this tent too.
She wanted to show herself.
Now...
have you heard of the sword of goodness?
Tell me.
Once upon a time, there was
a generous Sultan.
This Sultan heard that there was someone
more generous than him.
He was so angry!
Who is this man who is
more generous than me, he said.
Sultan was...
becoming more jealous and jealous.
Then...
he said his executioner that
he should kill that man!
I have to be the most generous
man in this world, he said.
Have some.
You too.
Enjoy it.
- Shouldn't you thank her?
- Thank you.
Sultan sent...
the executioner to the man.
However...
the executioner was
the guest of the man who he would kill.
He was treated so well by this man.
Then he learnt that he
was the man who he would kill!
May it be easy.
Zoe.
Thank you.
I wonder what happens at the end of the
story that Kumral Abdal tells.
I know what happens.
Kumral Abdal has told me once.
You should tell me one day.
Of course, I will.
I see you love children.
Of course I do.
Their cheeks are sweeter than sherbet.
They are the guests coming from
the heaven.
The guest from the heaven.
I should go now.
You couldn't say it again!
When will you tell her, Göktuğ?
When the executioner
returns, Sultan asked him.
Did you kill him, he asked.
He said no. I died, not him.
Sultan asked why.
I got to know this noble man.
He cut me with his...
generosity, with his
friendliness and hospitality.
He cut me with his
sword of goodness, the executioner said.
My Bala.
If you want to get through this...
use the sword of goodness.
You disappointed my father, Nikola.
What I will say now are the words
of my father, not mine.
If I was him, I would make
you a shepherd.
Doing things with Governor Yargucu, huh?
You waste your enemies.
You behave like Mongols'
leading Bey, not the Emperor's!
I do everything to win.
I am surprised that you don't know that
everything can be done to win.
Enough! Don't try to cover your failures.
It's in vain.
You lost Kalanoz and his army.
How long will we tolerate you?
Turks are more powerful than before
because of you!
Osman's successes attract Turks.
Osman is getting more powerful.
Even if I am alone...
I will kill Osman.
As for our Emperor...
if he wants to dismiss me...
he can.
I did whatever I could for this to happen.
However, my father wants to
give you one last chance.
Come here.
İznik.
It's important for us.
We shouldn't let Turks get there
like Suleiman ibn Qutalmish did.
We seek help from Crusades to
get Turks out of İznik.
However, this led us to lose
Constantinople.
If we don't take the necessary measures...
we will be in danger.
What is the Emperor's order?
Patrol unions are present through
Bilecik, İnegöl, Yarhisar and İznik.
You will encamp with governors.
Then the governors won't pay
taxes to Seljuq.
What will Geyhatu say about it?
Geyhatu is in the war.
We are sure he won't divide
his army for another war.
This war isn't between me and Osman.
It is between Byzantine and Seljuqs.
What about the army you send me?
Dukas, commander of Trakya unions.
He's on his way.
Dukas is our most skillful commander.
He will support you with his army.
Nikola.
I suggest you forget the
disagreements between each other.
Go now.
Tell everyone to prepare for the big war.
You will prepare them for the war.
Victory, Nikola.
It will make your our powerful commander.
And defeat will not only
disappoint my father...
but also you will
pay for it with your life.
I won't disappoint our Emperor.
Nikola, I hope.
I know why you're sad.
Am I?
Yes.
I know you.
I understand you.
Why am I sad, then?
You tell me.
Say what you want to say, Gonca.
We didn't need her doweries.
We didn't.
Won't you say something?
Osman Bey is okay with it.
We can't say anything.
- However...
- Gonca.
Enough.
We're here for justice.
Don't be shy.
Tell us what happened.
As I said before, I changed my mind.
I decided to sell my property
to Osman Bey.
Don't trick yourself...
as he can't defend himself.
Allah sees you and hears you.
Tell us now.
What happened between you two?
My Bey.
He didn't want to sell
his property that day...
I was so angry.
I took it as an insult to our Bey.
Then I....
forced him to sell his property.
I said I'd beat him...
if he wouldn't sell his property.
Beat him?
Forgive me, my Bey.
Did it happen?
Yes.
We should punish Boran...
as he threatened him and forced him...
to do something.
I have consent, my Sheikh.
You will keep your property.
And he will be given ten golds...
as he was oppressed.
You won't pay taxes to Seljuqs anymore.
I and the Emperor will protect you.
What does the Emperor want from us?
The Emperor wants your blood.
A war will happen soon
and there will be so much blood.
However, with the victory, we will
take our honor and...
our lands that Turks defeated back.
What about the army?
Will the Emperor send an army?
He will.
Who will lead the army?
Dukas.
That's good news, Governor Nikola.
Dukas is a big commander.
It's time to get it from his son.
We are late.
We won't pay taxes to Turks.
And a powerful commander will support us.
Turks are done.
Leo.
Why don't you say anything?
I don't want to be in this war.
Do you hear yourself?
Ending the trade and
making Geyhatu angry...
won't make us any good.
While Turks harm our
soldiers, our lands and our honor...
how can you talk about trade, Leo?
You should be angry towards Turks.
Nikola asked me what do
I think and I answered.
Kepp your thoughts, Leo.
If you don't side with us
and be against our Emperor...
you will be seen as a Turk.
My Bey.
My Bey, it won't happen again.
I have learnt my lesson.
Forgive me.
Your regret and sorrow...
shows that...
you pay for what you do.
As for the golds...
you're my Alp...
I will take care of that.
Osman Bey.
Today, I have learned what justice means.
I have seen how a ruler should be.
Please, Osman Bey.
Buy my property.
I want to sell it.
I will be honored if you accept.
Then...
I will pay double.
You're welcome.
My Bey.
From the governor.
Boran, come on.
You will rise, Osman Bey.
My friend.
If Köprühisar falls, İnegöl
l will be the next.
You know that so well.
We won't let that happen.
I trust you and your soldiers.
What worries me is Leo.
I have known Leo since he was a child.
Persuade him before Dukas comes.
What if I fail?
Then, I'll do what is necessary.
Don't worry, Nikola.
You can trust me.
I trust you, my friend.
Why are you so nervous?
It's good that Dukas
is coming with an army.
Helen.
This is my last opportunity.
If I fail...
the Emperor will kill
me before Osman does.
Dukas is coming for your victory.
A good commander, Dukas, will serve you.
The Emperor won't touch you.
If I lose...
the Emperor will kill me by an
assassinator or...
with poisonous wine.
You can go, Helen.
Helen.
Leo.
Tell them to follow Leo.
I can't just trust Atnos.
Find some spies for us. I
want to learn what he does.
If he doesn't give up on his thoughts...
I will have to kill him.
Osman Bey.
What happened, Governor Leo?
Why are we hiding?
I am being followed.
I even deceived my closest soldiers
and came here.
What is Nikola doing again?
The Emperor sent his son Mikail
to İznik to see Nikola.
Then...
a big war is coming.
It's worse than
a war this time, Osman Bey.
The Emperor ordered that they won't pay
taxes to Seljuqs anymore.
They will fight not only with us...
but also with you.
A new army will come.
Commander Dukas will serve Nikola
with a big army.
- Who is Dukas?
- A brave commander...
from a noble family.
He has big victories.
And he hates Turks so much.
He will form a big line of defense
with the support of governors.
Everyone's life is in danger.
Be careful.
What about the other governors?
Can they take the risk for such a war?
I told Nicola that I don't take sides
in this war.
But the fat is in the fire now.
The other governors can't refuse Nicola
even after all the throttling...
we experienced.
Osman Bey, they don't want to
pay tax to Seljuqs.
This is why they can risk everything.
Kopruhisar's Governor Agnosise is the
best supporter of this war.
He trusts Ducas.
Governor Leo.
This means your life is in danger too.
He can't touch me as I am
coming from the family of Emperor.
But he'll want to get rid of me
in the first chance.
You should know that
you are not alone.
Everybody who stands against the cruelty
is my brother.
You should know that.
Malhun Hatun.
You don't seem well.
Is there anything wrong?
I'm fine.
I'm just a bit weak.
Can I come in Malhun Hatun?
Come Bala Hatun.
Let us be alone.
We have something to talk about.
We don't, Bala Hatun.
It is over.
Won't you stand up?
Don't you see I can't?
Come sit.
I am not here to argue.
As long as you know your limits...
I have no problem with you.
I know my limits, Bala Hatun.
I am a Hatun of this tent.
You were needed to unite
the two tribes.
Nothing else.
What is wrong with you?
You are not fine.
I am fine.
I am alright.
Malhun Hatun!
Zoe!
Alaca!
Malhun Hatun!
If you want to get through this,
use sword of goodness.
Hatuns!
Malhun Hatun!
Hatuns! Bring the healer Hatuns!
Go!
Malhun Hatun!
We have valiant alps eyvallah (for sure).
We'll overcome this too, my Bey.
Let's hope for the best.
Eventually...
this will lead us to war.
However, even if we win...
we'll not have the same power
as before.
Both the Emperor and Nicola
are taking risk.
This war will not be ours.
It'll be Seljuqs'.
I'll go to Sultan.
I'll go to Sultan but..
I don't have much hope.
Why, my Bey?
He still has an army even though
he is under Geyhatu's order.
While everywhere in Anatolia is
full of rebels...
hoping for an army is just a dream,
Master Davut.
Even if we lose...
they cannot exile us from our land
so easily.
The order is Emperors...
But the land is ours.
We'll fight until the last
drop of our blood.
We prefer dying one thousand times
to give them an inch of land!
Brother, talk to all of the Beys.
But don't tell them where
the information is coming from.
Everybody shall get ready with
their alps for a huge war.
As you order, Osman Bey.
Excuse me.
Eyvallah (thank you).
My Lord...
give us power.
- Osman Bey!
- Bala!
Tell me.
You look pale.
Malhun Hatun.
- What happened to Malhun Hatun?
- She is not alright.
Healer Hatuns are taking care of her.
I summoned the doctor in Sogut.
What do you mean Bala?
Malhun Hatun.
Are you fine.
I am fine, Osman Bey, don't worry.
Fine.
Good, thank Lord.
- Osman Bey.
- Yes?
I have an important thing to say.
What's it?
Good news, Bey of Kayi.
You won't yearn for a child anymore.
What do you mean Malhun Hatun?
I am carrying the son of Ertugrul Ghazi
Osman Bey's son.
in my belly.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com